PAUL **CLARKE**

22455 Arcadia Court, Boca Raton, FL 33433 | H: 561-308-1149 | pclarke@bellsouth.net

SUMMARY

Operations management and project consulting, using innovative technology, to maximize efficiency of medium to large size businesses. Served as CTO responsibilities for companies on a temporary or permanent time-frame. Provide disaster and recovery plans. Designed and implemented software for full vertical solutions from sales, back office, accounting, secularization, and reports. Integrated accounting software with servicing platforms.

EXPERIENCE

07/1999 to Current

President

Beacon Consulting — Boca Raton, FL

20 Plus years experience providing companies both technological and operational leadership and guidance. Perform complete business and financial analyses including operations, process, procedures, and accounting systems, disaster recovery, hurricane preparations. Served as CTO for companies performing duties and tasks for Operations and Technology. Liaison with audit companies for internal and external audits including accounting and business practice for investor reports.

- Perform complete business and financial analyses including operations, process, procedures, and accounting systems, disaster recovery, hurricane preparations. Provided to companies COO duties and tasks
- Manage software design, training, and implementation for 200-person company
- Develop specialized reports for revenue analysis
- Create disaster recovery systems, call centers, and databases
- Designed and tested hurricane plans, for multi contingency and off site recovery
- Identify and coordinate hardware and software upgrade, moves, cloud changes and migrations
- Developed specialized functionality for portfolio reporting, calculations for valuations, scenario calculations based on criteria, threshold or trigger warnings for default
- Created functionality between servicing system platform and accounting software
- Created servicing system to manage billion dollar portfolio with ability to process lock boxes, ACH, wire transfers. Manage default triggers.
 Calculate scenario based on input criteria. Analyze data for marketing potential. Reporting for Investors and auditors
- Oversaw strategic business decision-making to develop, enhance and enforce business mission. Incorporated plans to standardized platforms and procedures for new company acquisitions.
- Oversaw strategic business decision-making to develop move to cloud based systems for parent company and all sister companies.
- Buildout Office Construction: Managed 100,000 square foot build out office projects in Miami and Ft Lauderdale. Worked extensively with Architect,

Building Owner, GC, Additional Subs. Maintained budgets, and build out calendar. Worked with design firm on furniture, office layout, specialty systems

10/2017 to 01/2018 Consultant

SuttonPark Captial — Boca Raton, FL

01/2018 to 12/2018 Consultant

777 Partners — Miami, FL

01/2000 to 10/2017 Consultant

SingerAsset Finance — Boca Raton, FL

12/1996 to 05/1998 Database Administrator

LRP Publications — Palm Beach Gardens, FL

- Performed comparative analysis of Department of Labor's 1.2 million record database
- Customized software products for national 401 K and brokerage companies
- Created and maintained 200,000 record database
- Developed marketing strategies for database products and provided customer support
- Established vendor contacts to develop front-end database application

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Science: Operation Managment **Boston University** — Boston, MA, United States